## SCOTT E. SMITH

Newport Beach, CA 92663 • tel. (949) 673-3048 • Scott@VirtualBS.com

**Professional Summary** 

Accomplished Full-Stack, React Developer with real-world experience in business process development, programming and execution. A full range of experience from programming the bits, bytes & blocks (that's right I drank the Kool-aid) to delivering a finished product to the consumer.

### Technical Skills

- Design Graphics, Inkscape, Gimp
- Video Production & Motion Graphics, Premiere, After Effects
- Marketing: Facebook, Youtube, Adwords
- Php, Java MVC
- Javascript, jQuery, React
- C++, Visual Studio & Unity
- Html, CSS, BootStrap, Semantic-UI
- MySQL, MongoDb, SQL Server
- AWS & Github

Recent Project Experience

#### **David Q. Trivia .com** June 2017 - Present

Now you too can be a YouTuber! In this project I employed Php & Php API's to generate a video from a trivia question entered thru our website. Our members submit their favorite trivia questions and receive a percentage of the YouTube revenues from our viewership. We also give away a \$100 Paypal gift certificate each month based on a members participation in submitting questions, voting on questions to publish and playing our bi-weekly trivia scratcher.

# **CubeTic – Video Game** Mar 2016 – May 2017

A completely new video game process on a more complex version of the world's oldest game. CubeTic is a social networked casual video game, think "Words with Friends". It was developed on Unity 3D and PlayFab backend services. Unity allows it to be developed for both gaming platforms and on all devices. It is integrated with facebook for multi-player capability and communicates with all social network sites.

## Video Directions Jun 2014 – Sept 2015

Providing highly customizable mapped directions for enhanced customer service in the "Last Mile" of computer-based navigation and Logistics. Interactive Google Maps javascript overlay with embedded video and customizable track maintenance.

Education